On the path of destiny I have beaten all the enemies
Na drodze przeznaczenia pokonałem wszystkich wrogów
I have gained fame and respect from the gods
Zdobyłem sławę i szacunek bogów
They often call me the Dragon Slayer
Zabójcą smoków mnie często nazywają
I have banished The Sleeper everyone remembers that
Wygnałem Śniącego, o tym wszyscy pamiętają
But there is one figh, that I dream about every night
Jest jednak walka, która śni mi się po nocach
In the old fortress, the one with dark powers
W Starej Fortecy, tej o czarnych mocach
the enemy there is more terrifying than Beliar
Tamten przeciwnik jest straszniejszy od Beliara
the damned Ladder, is the one that defeated me
To przeklęta drabina, to ta co mnie pokonała
This is the infernal image of death
To piekielny obraz śmierci
I want to remove it from my memory
Chcę wyrzucić go z pamięci
What happened? Did I fall?
Co się stało, czy ja spadłem?
Soon I will fall into depression
Zaraz w depresję popadnę
A nightmarish depiction of misery
To koszmarny obraz nędzy
Soon you will taste my revenge
Wkrótce zaznasz mojej zemsty
Power of the fist, no mercy
Siła pięści, brak litości
so I will beat the hell out of you
Więc porachuję ci kości
This is the infernal image of death
To piekielny obraz śmierci
I want to remove it from my memory
Chcę wyrzucić go z pamięci
What happened? Did I fall?
Co się stało, czy ja spadłem?
Soon I will fall into depression
Zaraz w depresję popadnę
it's a nightmarish depiction of misery
To koszmarny obraz nędzy
Soon you will taste my revenge
Wkrótce zaznasz mojej zemsty
Power of the fist, no mercy
Siła pięści, brak litości
so I will beat the hell out of you
Więc porachuję ci kości
No! By Innos! I sense a presence of a dark being, something very evil. A grim force flows through the whole valley.
Nie, na Innosa! Wyczuwam tu obecność czegoś mrocznego, czegoś bardzo złego. Ponura moc wypełnia całą dolinę.
I have met the Ladder. I'm afraid I am going to die imminently.
Spotkałem drabinę. Boję się, że zaraz zginę.
This is your greatest enemy
To twój największy wróg
Because of whom you fall from the top to the bottom
Przez niego spadasz z góry w dół
Your greatest enemy
Twój największy wróg
You may start digging your grave right away
Już możesz kopać sobie grób
Because of whom you fall from the top again
Przez niego spadasz z góry znów
Your greatest enemy
Twój największy wróg
This game is one hell of a BUG!
Ta gra to jeden wielki BUG!
This is the infernal image of death
To piekielny obraz śmierci
I want to remove it for my memory
Chcę wyrzucić go z pamięci
What happened? Did I fall?
Co się stało, czy ja spadłem?
Soon I will fall into depression
Zaraz w depresję popadnę
it's a nightmarish depiction of misery
To koszmarny obraz nędzy
Soon you will taste my revenge
Wkrótce zaznasz mojej zemsty
Power of the fist, no mercy
Siła pięści, brak litości
so I will beat the hell out of you
Więc porachuję ci kości
This is the infernal image of death
To piekielny obraz śmierci
I want to remove it for my memory
Chcę wyrzucić go z pamięci
What happened? Did I fall?
Co się stało, czy ja spadłem?
Soon I will fall into depression
Zaraz w depresję popadnę
it's a nightmarish depiction of misery
To koszmarny obraz nędzy
Soon you will taste my revenge
Wkrótce zaznasz mojej zemsty
Power of the fist, no mercy
Siła pięści, brak litości
so I will beat the hell out of you
Więc porachuję ci kości